<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My blogs on Portfolio website for Nicolas Bossers</title>
    <link>/blogs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in My blogs on Portfolio website for Nicolas Bossers</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/blogs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CV</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog2/</guid>
      <description>My international work and study experiences, charity work and hobbies:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pay discrimination</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Omega Group plc- Is there pay discrimination in the company?
At the last board meeting of Omega Group Plc., the headquarters of a large multinational company, the issue was raised that women were being discriminated in the company, in the sense that the salaries were not the same for male and female executives. A quick analysis of a sample of 50 employees (of which 24 men and 26 women) revealed that the average salary for men was about 8,700 higher than for women.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spielburg vs Burton</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog3/</guid>
      <description>I would like you to explore whether the mean IMDB rating for Steven Spielberg and Tim Burton are the same or not. I will run a hypothesis test and calculate the confidence intervals for the mean ratings of these two directors.
Null and alternative hypothesis:
H0: The difference in the mean IMDB ratings for Steven Spielberg and Tim Burton is equal to zero.
H1: The difference in the mean IMDB ratings for Steven Spielberg and Tim Burton is not equal to zero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US, Germany and India</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog4/</guid>
      <description>GDP components over time and among countries:
At the risk of oversimplifying things, the main components of gross domestic product, GDP are personal consumption (C), business investment (I), government spending (G) and net exports (exports - imports).
The GDP data we will look at is from the United Nations’ National Accounts Main Aggregates Database, which contains estimates of total GDP and its components for all countries from 1970 to today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
